const essentialsChapter20QuizData = [
  {
    id: "20_1",
    question: "Carbon Monoxide (CO) and Smoke Detectors may be battery-powered while others operate from household current. (Page 251)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "20_2",
    question: "_________ is colorless, odorless, and tasteless. Humans cannot detect its presence. (Page 252)",
    options: ["Carbon Monoxide", "Creosote", "Smoke", "Sulfur"],
    answer: "Carbon Monoxide"
  },
  {
    id: "20_3",
    question: "According to the Chimney Safety Institute of America (CSIA), having one carbon monoxide and smoke detector for each level of the home is unnecessary. (Page 252)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    id: "20_4",
    question: "How often should you test a smoke detector? (Page 252)",
    options: ["Daily", "Monthly", "Quarterly", "Yearly"],
    answer: "Monthly"
  },
  {
    id: "20_5",
    question: "_________ are more responsive to slow, smoldering fires and smoke. (Page 252)",
    options: ["Photoelectric Sensors", "Ionization Detectors", "People", "Carbon Monoxide Detectors"],
    answer: "Photoelectric Sensors"
  },
  {
    id: "20_6",
    question: "_________ are more responsive to fast flaming fires. (Page 252)",
    options: ["Photoelectric Sensors", "Ionization Detectors", "People", "Carbon Monoxide Detectors"],
    answer: "Ionization Detectors"
  },
  {
    id: "20_7",
    question: "_________ fire extinguishers are designed to put out fires of things commonly found in the home such as wood and paper, grease, oils and gasoline and electrically charged fires. (Page 252)",
    options: ["ABC", "K", "Class D", "Wet Chemical"],
    answer: "ABC"
  },
  {
    id: "20_8",
    question: "This class of fire extinguisher is for Solids (wood, cloth, paper). (Page 252)",
    options: ["A", "B", "C"],
    answer: "A"
  },
  {
    id: "20_9",
    question: "This class of fire extinguisher is for Liquids (gasoline, oil, paint). (Page 252)",
    options: ["A", "B", "C"],
    answer: "B"
  },
  {
    id: "20_10",
    question: "This class of fire extinguisher is for Energized Electrical Equipment (appliances, wiring). (Page 252)",
    options: ["A", "B", "C"],
    answer: "C"
  },
  {
    id: "20_11",
    question: "A common way to warm up a flue is to use a lit 'newspaper torch'. (Page 252)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "20_12",
    question: "Always keep the fireplace damper closed when lighting a fire. (Page 253)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    id: "20_13",
    question: "The cross-sectional area of a round flue should be _________ the size of the fireplace opening. (Page 253)",
    options: ["1/12", "1/20", "1/10", "1/8"],
    answer: "1/12"
  },
  {
    id: "20_14",
    question: "The cross-sectional area of a square or rectangular flue with an aspect ratio of less than 2:1 should be _________ the size of the fireplace opening. (Page 253)",
    options: ["1/12", "1/20", "1/10", "1/8"],
    answer: "1/10"
  },
  {
    id: "20_15",
    question: "The cross-sectional area of a square or rectangular flue with an aspect ratio of more than 2:1 should be _________ the size of the fireplace opening. (Page 253)",
    options: ["1/12", "1/20", "1/10", "1/8"],
    answer: "1/8"
  },
  {
    id: "20_16",
    question: "A fireplace opening is 36 inches x 24 inches. Out of the options below, what size square or rectangle flue is the best to use? (Page 253)",
    options: ["8 x 8", "8 x 12", "10 x 10", "12 x 12"],
    answer: "8 x 12"
  },
  {
    id: "20_17",
    question: "A fireplace opening is 36 inches x 24 inches. Out of the options below, what size round flue is the best to use? (Page 253)",
    options: ["8 inch", "6 inch", "10 inch", "12 inch"],
    answer: "10 inch"
  },
  {
    id: "20_18",
    question: "A fireplace opening has an 8 x 17 flue. Out of the options below, what size fireplace opening is the max that the flue could handle? (Page 253)",
    options: ["36 inches x 24 inches", "48 inches x 24 inches", "40 inches x 26 inches", "38 inches x 24 inches"],
    answer: "40 inches x 26 inches"
  },
  {
    id: "20_19",
    question: "Premature deterioration of the firebox and liner or mortar joints in a masonry fireplace may be a result of _________. (Page 254)",
    options: ["Water Entry", "High Draft", "Low Pressure", "Burning wood with 25% moisture content"],
    answer: "Water Entry"
  },
  {
    id: "20_20",
    question: "We can claim that we can correct odors. (Page 254)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    id: "20_21",
    question: "Chimney odors are most noticeable when the interior of the chimney is _________. (Page 254)",
    options: ["Dry", "Wet"],
    answer: "Wet"
  },
  {
    id: "20_22",
    question: "Which of the following provide a better seal? (Page 254)",
    options: ["Top Mount Damper", "Throat Damper", "Connector Damper"],
    answer: "Top Mount Damper"
  },
  {
    id: "20_23",
    question: "You should advise the homeowner that they should never burn anything in a wood stove not specifically allowed by the manufacturer. (Page 255)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "20_24",
    question: "The first thing you should do if there is a chimney fire is to exit immediately and call 911. (Page 255)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "20_25",
    question: "Most chimney fires are noticed. (Page 255)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    id: "20_26",
    question: "If a homeowner suspects they have had a chimney fire, they should have a CSIA Certified Technician perform, at minimum, a _________ inspection. (Page 255)",
    options: ["Level 1", "Level II", "Level III"],
    answer: "Level II"
  },
  {
    id: "20_27",
    question: "The best location for a large volume of wood is _________. (Page 256)",
    options: ["Outside under cover", "In the basement", "In an open area uncovered", "Directly next to the fireplace"],
    answer: "Outside under cover"
  },
  {
    id: "20_28",
    question: "A cord of wood is _________. (Page 256)",
    options: ["48 inches wide x 48 inches tall x 96 inches long/deep", "48 inches wide x 96 inches tall x 96 inches long/deep", "96 inches wide x 96 inches tall x 96 inches long/deep", "48 inches wide x 48 inches tall x 48 inches long/deep"],
    answer: "48 inches wide x 48 inches tall x 96 inches long/deep"
  },
  {
    id: "20_29",
    question: "A rick or face cord is _________. (Page 256)",
    options: ["1/3 of a cord", "1/2 of a cord", "3/4 of a cord", "1/4 of a cord"],
    answer: "1/3 of a cord"
  },
  {
    id: "20_30",
    question: "A 'top down' fire consists of the smaller pieces of wood on the bottom and the larger pieces on top. (Page 256)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    id: "20_31",
    question: "One of the benefits of a 'top down' fire is _________. (Page 256)",
    options: ["You use less wood", "By design, it preheats the flue which reduces spillage", "It produces a full fire faster", "It is faster"],
    answer: "By design, it preheats the flue which reduces spillage"
  },
  {
    id: "20_32",
    question: "For coal stoves, never add more coal unless there is already a hot fire in the combustion chamber. (Page 257)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "20_33",
    question: "Ashes should be placed in _________. (Page 257)",
    options: ["A metal bucket inside", "A metal bucket outside", "In a trash bag", "A plastic bucket outside"],
    answer: "A metal bucket outside"
  },
  {
    id: "20_34",
    question: "NFPA 211 requires that the venting system be inspected annually and cleaned, maintained and repaired as necessary. (Page 257)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "20_35",
    question: "You should use a non-abrasive glass cleaner designed for creosote removal when the doors are still hot. (Page 258)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    id: "20_36",
    question: "You can install a new gasket directly over the old one. (Page 258)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    id: "20_37",
    question: "Stove paint should be rated to withstand _________. (Page 258)",
    options: ["900°F", "1000°F", "1100°F", "2000°F"],
    answer: "1100°F"
  },
  {
    id: "20_38",
    question: "The amount of light you can see coming through the gaps in the catalyst's surface is a good indication of how clean the catalyst is on a Catalytic Combustor. (Page 258)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "20_39",
    question: "It is illegal to operate a stove if the catalyst is deactivated or removed. (Page 259)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    id: "20_40",
    question: "What EPA program was designed to help educate the fireplace/appliance user on tips to burn wood more efficiently. (Page 259)",
    options: ["EPA Wood Burning Education", "EPA Burn Wise", "EPA Efficient Burning", "EPA Emission Lowering"],
    answer: "EPA Burn Wise"
  },
  {
    id: "20_41",
    question: "If you don't know the answer to something, DO NOT FABRICATE ONE! (Page 260)",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True"
  },
];


if (!window.quizRegistry) window.quizRegistry = {};
window.quizRegistry['Chapter 20: Advising the Customer and Maintenance'] = essentialsChapter20QuizData;
